Contact

stephaniestinnett@ymail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-glenn-38a6025b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Perioperative Nursing ACLS BLS

Stephanie Glenn

Operating Room Nurse at Emerald Health Services Napa, California

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Post Anesthesia Care, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), and Prevention. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelors of Science focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from University of Nevada-Reno.

Experience

Emerald Health Services
Operating Room Nurse
July 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)
San Francisco Bay Area

Renown Health
Nurse Circulator
November 2013 - Present (6 years 9 months)
reno, nevada

Humboldt General Hospital Perioperative Nurse January 2013 - November 2013 (11 months)

- Identifies, assesses and diagnoses problems through patient assessment and interactions; and evaluates actual or potential patient health problems.
- Assesses, plans and implements interventions for solving patient care problems.
- Formulates care plans for specific patients and documents the nursing process in patient's record.
- Evaluates patient response to interventions and modifies plan of care as needed to achieve health care goals.
- Develops and participates in educating patients, their families, or significant others about post discharge care programs.
- Initiates patient care meetings with the health care team to revise the plan of care as the patient's condition warrants.

- Maintains a safe and therapeutic patient care environment.
- Provides guidance and direction to members of the health care team to ensure quality patient care.
- Keeps current on advances in nursing care by participating in educational programs.
- Provides and oversees direct patient care in accordance with established nursing protocol and physicians' orders.
- Utilizes knowledge of medications, procedures, infection control, and safety precaution; and initiates appropriate interventions in crisis situations.
- Participates in total quality management to positively affect patient and system outcomes to improve care.

Passport Health

Travel Nurse Specialist October 2012 - January 2013 (4 months)

- Monitor, record, and report symptoms or changes in patients' conditions.
- Provide immunizations for individuals who plan to study abroad or travel overseas.
- Instruct individuals, families, or other groups on topics such as health education and prevention.

Education

University of Nevada-Reno

Bachelors of Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2011)

Truckee Meadows Community College

Associate of Science (A.S.), Biology, General · (2006 - 2008)